samuraibuyer.jp 2017-07-14

# Privacy policy | SAMURAI BUYER engages in transfer service and proxy shopping service for all Japanese Goods by international shipping

SAMURAI BUYER provides a delivery service that delivers goods from Japan via a Japanese shop online to residential addresses overseas

SAMURAI INTERNATIONAL LIMITED ("the Company") handles a range of personal information, including information about customers and clients, as part of its business activities.   
The company is committed to the proper protection of personal information. Samurai Buyer is a company dedicated to running the business of Proxy Shopping, transfer and delivery of good to overseas destinations.

### 1\. About the acquisition of the personal information

The company has acquired your personal or company information which it assumes is just not false.

### 2\. Use of personal information

The Company may use Personal Information, including your name, address, telephone number, date of birth, email address, and other information including details of your transactions with us, for the following purposes The company will use it on your agreement for the exclusive of the purposes below  
（１）The sale of our products; surveys; and other promotional information  
（２）Shipping and Proxy Shopping of ordered goods and procedures  
（３）The provision of seminar, recommended goods and promotional information

### 3\. Security of personal information

The company takes every legal prevention to avoid leaking personal information and loss or defamation.

### 4\. Provision of personal information

The Company will strictly adhere to the Privacy requirements in each country when it comes to trust and the disclosure of personal information 

### 5\. Provision of personal information to third party

The Company takes appropriate steps to protect personal information and shall not disclose nor provide it to a third party in a form that allows an individual to be identified without the consent of that individual, except where allowed by the Personal Information Protection Law, and other laws and regulations.

### 6\. Disclosing and correcting personal information

The Company shall respond to requests for the disclosure, revision, addition, deletion, and discontinuation of use, elimination, cessation of provision to third parties and notification of purposes of use of personal information in accordance with the Personal Information Protection Law and other laws and regulations.   
If the request does not meet the requirements stipulated by the Personal Information Protection Law and the JISQ15001, the Company may be unable to respond to the request.

### 7\. Modify of Private Policy

The content of this private policy may modify.  
It is valid once the content has been cited.

Responsible person for Private Policy: SAMURAI INTERNATIONAL LIMITED Yasuharu Tanaka
